Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪That day♪
♪Nothing stays together forever♪
♪I've quit romance♪
♪Who hasn't failed again♪
♪Crying in death♪
♪And in life♪
♪Even now♪
♪We keep learning♪
♪It's no surprise♪
♪Being happy is so hard♪
♪Weirdly, I became a role model♪
♪On the day we met again, we said hi♪
♪It was a reminder,
a test, and a complaint♪
♪Who can do anything without regret♪
♪I am all right♪
♪May you live in peace♪
♪Let the world roar♪
♪Sounds like a carnival♪
♪Being alive is never dull♪
♪How wonderful to be free♪
♪I became even better without you♪
♪Nothing can be perfect♪
♪We bless each other in pain♪
♪We nod and smile♪
♪May we both be well♪
= Love's Ambition=
= Episode 4 =
You're from Shanxi, right?
Yes.
- Have you been to Dayun County?
- My grandma was from Yunlai Village
of Dayun County.
Now, Dayun County
has developed well.
It's changed a lot.
(Yunjiangli Commercial Street
Renovation Project Begins)
(Hello, Mr. Shen.)
(This is our representative)
(Qiao Jianbin.)
(Hello.)
By the way,
didn't you stay longer
on your business trip?
No,
I only cut the ribbon.
It was a quick trip.
Don't watch the news.
I want to watch cartoons.
Dad,
do you have time now?
I want to talk about
the old city renovation.
Sure.
Talk over there.
Haochen.
I've told you many times
it will damage your eyes.
Qiao!
Meal is ready!
After I finish these two rollers,
I'll come.
- You are here, Yazhen.
- Ms. Sha, getting a perm?
Yes.
Yazhen,
Qiao is quite popular now.
On TV,
he spoke so eloquently,
even upstaging the county mayor!
Of course.
With all these stores around,
they let me
be the merchant representative.
I had to do my best.
Right?
No wonder you raised
such good daughters.
The younger one
is working now?
What's the point?
She never calls,
and only sends a text
during holidays.
Lin is better.
She stays
with us.
She is our sweet daughter.
Right.
Is Lin
about to marry soon?
Very soon.
My future son-in-law
is going to be a banker.
Beauty.
I work at Dayun County's
largest fertilizer factory.
I am responsible for holiday
group purchase benefits.
Add me on WeChat.
If I need to purchase,
I'll tell you.
Feel free to come
to our counter.
Take this.
You are so rigid.
How can you make money?
Many salesgirls want my contact,
yet they can't get it.
Your hands are so fair.
Are you insane?
I'll pick you up after work.
You!
Stop there!
Don't touch me.
Honey.
She hit me!
Why did you hit him?
Why did you hit me?
You wretch!
Are you insane?
Let go of me!
What's going on?
Let go!
I'll report you!
(Police)
Lin.
We agreed to discuss
the wedding at my place.
Dad. Mom.
We're back.
Troublemaker.
How dare you come!
Auntie. I...
Lin.
Dad.
Here.
Have some fruits.
Dad.
This is the money from you
(Details of wedding costs)
and my mom for our marriage.
Excluding the betrothal money
for Lin family,
wedding rings,
and other
expenses,
there is still 98,654 yuan.
I'll ask one question.
What about the cash gifts?
You'll have it.
Lin and I agreed on this.
Let me break it down.
The wedding photos cost
9,588 yuan.
I chose a moderately
priced wedding planner,
costing 18,800 yuan.
For accommodation
for out-of-town guests,
I booked 20 standard rooms.
Each room costs 288 yuan,
totaling 5,760 yuan.
About the return gifts,
we'll prepare them.
15,000 yuan should suffice.
I booked 20 banquet tables.
Each table costs
1,288 yuan.
20 tables?
That's not enough.
Mom.
Our bank has rules.
For weddings,
not more than 20 tables are allowed.
No exceptions.
Otherwise, my superior and I
would be affected.
Did your bank mention
if your fiancee frequently visiting
police stations
would affect your career?
Auntie.
Get straight to the point.
Stop being so sarcastic,
okay?
I'm being sarcastic?
As a young woman,
you always cause trouble.
Why don't you
think of the consequences?
Do you live
in the police station?
You go there many times a month!
Auntie.
This wasn't my fault!
Today, that man
harassed me first.
Enough!
Be quiet.
Qiao Lin.
You're Lin Tao's fiancee.
Our town is small.
If you keep causing trouble
and word gets out,
it'll affect Tao's career.
Understand?
If his career gets affected,
you'll be affected too.
My son
graduated from a top university
with a master's degree.
He's a bank client manager now,
and will become a department head,
branch manager, and even bank president!
Look at you.
You're ruining my son's
bright future!
We are to blame
for accepting your marriage.
Lin. I've calculated it.
We still
have 17,866 yuan.
It's enough
for our honeymoon.
Enjoy it yourself.
Lin.
(- What're you doing?)
(- At work. What's wrong?)
(Nothing.)
(When will you come home?)
Lin.
Have an apple.
Thanks, Dad.
Dad.
Have you used the betrothal money
from Lin Tao?
Yes.
We agreed to use
the money for renovating the new store.
After we sell the old store,
we'll return it to you.
What now?
Did Lin Tao's parents
say anything?
Not exactly.
I'm Just asking.
How's your wedding
preparations going?
He's been busy with work.
I've been busy lately too.
Right.
I need to go on a business trip soon.
A study trip
in Jingzhou.
To Jingzhou?
How long?
Have you told Lin Tao?
Not yet.
Wait.
Lin.
You should at least
inform Lin Tao about the trip.
Lin Tao is a key talent
at the bank now.
He has his pride.
You need to get along well.
Exactly.
You're about to get married.
You should be considerate.
Understand?
You should
discuss everything with Lin Tao.
You hear me?
Yes.
Right.
You two should live
a peaceful life together.
Just stay
with us.
Don't be like your sister.
This daughter
is like she never exists.
♪I'll make you adore me,
let the spotlight be mine♪
♪Like a raw diamond,
my presence shapes the world♪
♪Blooming in my colors,
every frame's perfection♪
♪My beauty's defined by none
but my own command♪
♪Let the spotlight be mine♪
The list and procedures
of the Family Feast
need double-checking.
Contact me immediately
if you need me.
Alright.
Yan.
We have
a gathering tonight.
Want to join us?
I'll pass.
My boyfriend will come.
Boyfriend?
He is your fiance, right?
Go home early tonight, alright?
Okay.
Have a good date tonight.
I'm leaving.
Yan.
Qiao Yan!
I am so lucky today, meeting you
right after work.
Otherwise,
I couldn't find you.
- Why are you here?
- I called off the wedding.
I'm now free from all worries,
so I thought to try my luck
in a big city.
I haven't found a place.
Can I go to your place?
There's a cafe opposite.
Let's talk there.
Alright.
No need for cafe.
What a waste.
Let's go.
We can talk
in your place.
Yan.
Your boyfriend?
My future brother-in-law?
Hi.
This is...
I'm...
My cousin.
She came to me.
Hello.
I'm picking her up for dinner.
Want to join us?
She just arrived,
and is a bit tired.
I'll find a hotel
to settle her in.
Alright.
We can only
go to the restaurant another day.
Okay?
Okay.
Go home then.
I'll call you
when I get home.
Go.
Bye then.
Be careful.
Drive safely.
The place is great
with convenient transportation.
Qiao Yan. Why did you say
I'm your cousin?
There's a refrigerator.
A convenience store is nearby.
I can see it now.
Your boyfriend
is well-off,
so you look down on
me, a loser,
right?
Go back soon.
What do you mean?
You canceled the wedding,
and didn't tell our parents.
They'll search for you.
Right.
After I get settled,
I'll tell them then.
It's the same.
Wait, get back to the point.
I'm asking you
why you didn't tell your boyfriend
I'm your elder sister.
Grandma and I share
a household registration.
My surname is Xu,
not Qiao.
So,
you should know
my only family
is Grandma.
Right.
I know you've never been
close with our parents.
But I never thought
we weren't family.
Only you think so.
Qiao Lin.
You came here
without telling me.
What I've done for you
is already more than enough.
Go home after running
out of money.
Don't make them worry.
You can stay if you want,
but I'm not obligated
to take care of you.
Qiao Yan.
Had I known it,
I would've
never come to you.
Understand?
My surname is Xu.
Xu Yan.
You are Qiao Yan.
You are Qiao Yan! Qiao...
(Transfer to Qiao Lin)
(The price of your heartlessness.)
So heartless!
I shouldn't have saved you back then!
- Wild child!
Wild child.
Wild child!
- Wild child!
Move! Let me go home!
Qiao Yan, unwanted one.
Wild child, without parents!
How dare you push me?
None of your business!
Who dares bully my sister?
Do you dare?
- No.
You're my sister now.
Yan is old enough
to start elementary school,
and she must start studying.
You must find her
a primary school in the county.
All these years,
as parents,
you've never fulfilled
your responsibilities.
But regarding the school enrollment,
both of you must
make every effort
to make it right.
Right, Mom.
We came here
to take Yan back
for attending the school.
All these years,
you've been raising her alone,
and it's been hard.
Enough!
Save your sweet talk.
Do you even know
what Yan tells
the neighborhood
and kids?
She says her parents
are abroad.
How did such a young child
learn to lie?
After having Lin,
you insisted on trying for a boy.
You knew perfectly well
Yazhen has poor health.
These years
her health is completely ruined.
Now you've got a girl,
with congenital heart disease,
and you don't like her.
Won't you even
save her life?
As parents,
don't you feel any guilt?
Mom.
We know we were wrong.
We will treat Yan well
and make it up for her
after taking her back.
Mom.
Be careful.
Alright.
We're home.
Come in.
This is Mom and Dad's home.
From now on, it's yours too.
From today on,
share this room
with your elder sister.
Okay?
I will bring in
your luggage.
I packed these pretty clothes
for you.
At Mom and Dad's place,
be sensible and obedient.
Do things yourself
whenever possible.
I also packed these things you like
for you.
At mealtimes,
don't fight with your sister.
Understand?
I will miss you.
Take a look.
This is your home now.
Alright, it's late.
Let's bathe and sleep.
Come on, I will bathe you.
Mom, I can bathe myself.
Alright.
You can bathe yourself.
Then,
take off the clothes
and I will wash them. Okay?
Mom, I can wash my clothes.
Why is the smell of gas so strong?
Lin!
Wake up! Don't scare me!
What?
Help!
Help! Help!
What's going on?
Gas poisoning!
Lin, wake up!
Lin!
Call the ambulance!
Okay, stay calm.
Lin!
Wake up! Wake up!
Don't scare me.
Lin.
Wake up, wake up. Lin!
Lin!
What's going on?
Qiao?
Lin has poisoned...
Where have you been?
You didn't turn off the gas.
Lin!
Lin, are you okay?
Stop shouting!
Go call an ambulance!
Qiao!
Where's Yan?
Yan!
Another one?
Help out!
It is all my fault.
I'm so sorry.
My daughter.
Here.
Have a banana.
Let Dad feed you.
Open your mouth.
One more bite. A big bite.
Come on.
Good girl.
I will make you
your favorite braised pork.
Okay?
(Qiao Yan: 12 years old,
Qiao Lin: 14 years old)
Yan!
Perfect timing.
Lin got into a fight.
We need to go there.
You can have instant noodles.
Qiao, hurry up!
(Happy birthday)
♪Happy birthday to you♪
♪Happy birthday♪
Yan? Is that you?
Happy birthday.
Grandma.
Alright, don't cry.
Come to my place.
I'll make you delicious food.
Okay?
You are
always getting into fights.
You even fought with a boy!
That's your classmate.
What if you hurt him?
See?
The teacher
always calls us in
to apologize.
Keep quiet.
She's asleep.
Compensate them,
treat them meals,
(Mom, Dad, I'm going to bed.)
and apologize!
(I've eaten. Don't worry.)
See?
Yan is well-behaved.
But you
spend all day fighting,
not giving us a break.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Alright.
You're hungry.
We're busy apologizing,
and haven't eaten.
Here.
I'll reheat this.
Come here.
What do you want? Noodles?
Okay.
I'm hungry.
Take a bath.
Mom.
Eat after your bath.
I'm hungry.
Bathe yourself.
I need to wash these clothes.
You need them tomorrow.
Wrap yourself up.
Don't catch a cold.
(Qiao Yan: 18 years old)
Qiao Yan obtained great scores
(Qiao Lin: 20 years old)
in recent mock exams.
She's ranked top 30 in her grade.
She can get into a top college
in Jingzhou.
As for the major,
you should
discuss it with her,
and guide her.
She can obtain
such outstanding results,
thanks to your dedicated guidance.
But, she won't attend
the college entrance exam.
We have other plans for her.
What?
Given her academic performance,
it would be a pity.
Have you
discussed this with her?
What does she think?
A child can't understand
our family's hardships.
I can decide this
for her.
Why forbid me from attending the exam?
I'm talking with your teacher.
Why forbid me
from attending the exam?
Because I'm your dad!
I'm the head of our family!
Sorry, Miss.
Sorry
for the embarrassment.
This decision is final.
Go home.
Why won't you let me attend the college?
Dad!
Dad, wait for me!
Wait!
Wait for me!
Why?
Because we're poor.
Because the expenses
for college are high,
and we can't support
two college students.
So we choose
to let Lin go to college.
Dad, what about me?
What about me?
After you finish high school,
we'll help you find a job.
This way, you can stay with us.
And we can take care of you.
Wait.
I...
I want to know why...
Why have you always been
so biased all the time?
Why does Qiao Lin
get all the good things?
Am I...
Am I not your biological child?
Why do you always make me feel
that you don't love me?
I thought if I kept lying to myself
and kept studying hard,
behaving well,
and listening to you,
you'd finally love me.
Why can't I keep lying to myself now?
What...
What have I ever wronged you?
We've provided you
everything you needed,
so why can't you be considerate?
You forbid me from attending the college
without consulting me!
What you're doing is theft!
What you're doing is robbery!
How dare you speak
to your dad like this!
So outrageous!
You will only be an ungrateful child
even with a college degree!
How horrible am I?
What terrible thing have I done?
I don't understand.
I don't understand
why you have to prove
how much you don't love me.
Why?
Why do I have to be your daughter?
Grandma.
Coming.
Yan.
You...
Grandma.
I know
you've been wronged.
Look, you're all wet.
(Incoming call from Shen Haoming)
Hello, Haoming.
- What are you doing?
- I'm on my way home.
Can you come to my studio?
Now?
Yes.
Hurry.
Okay.
Change the address, please.
What's wrong?
A flower stalk has grown?
This plant is sixty years old.
I think
tonight
it will bloom.
If it does bloom,
this will undoubtedly be
its most glorious moment.
I want to witness this with you.
I remember you once mentioned
the agave only blooms
once in its lifetime.
So after blooming,
it will die.
After blooming,
it will wither rapidly
and drain
until
returning to dust.
It has exhausted all the nutrients
throughout its life
and endured hardship
just for this moment to bloom.
This is truly
its swan song.
What's wrong?
I just feel
it is pitiful.
Its whole life
is spent battling hardships,
and growing tenaciously,
just for a single moment to bloom.
Because it has no choice.
It must
stay stronger,
work harder,
and endure more
than others to achieve
their beautiful endings.
Waiting for long
and suffering the torment
are all the price it pays.
Blossoming, fruiting,
aging, and being reborn
happen in cycles.
This is the law of nature.
But when each agave
blooms,
its pollen
scatters around,
and meets another agave.
They cross-pollinate
and produce more seeds.
These seeds
become
their legacy
in this world,
just like humans.
Meeting,
loving,
marrying, and having children.
A century later,
though the people
may be gone,
their love endures.
When two agaves meet,
they do everything
for each other,
even at the cost of their lives.
Because they know
their love
is worth it.
They never regret it.
Just like you and me.
Meeting you
and being with you.
No matter what price
I must pay,
I will never
regret it.
And you?
Think it carefully.
I do regret...
I regret getting married next month.
I should've married you earlier.
♪Let tears flow freely,
deep blue seas turn to foam♪
♪We regained freedom♪
♪If you ever remembered me,
that's enough♪
Let's also put this agave
in the decorative pond, okay?
Then it won't be lonely.
Okay.
♪I love you, that's right,
you changed me♪
♪We shed tears,
deep blue seas turn to foam♪
♪You found me♪
♪If you remember me, then I'm pleased♪
♪Like fireworks that loved,
rushing toward the stars, undaunted by pain♪
♪Fearless of flames,
even if just a fleeting sparkle♪
♪We shed tears,
deep blue seas turn to foam♪
♪We regained freedom♪
♪If you remember me, then I'm pleased♪
♪I just wanna take my time tonight♪
♪To do all the things I said I'd try♪
♪I go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different place♪
♪I go drink, go party, and go dance♪
♪Even if I'm lonely♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪